{
    "Easy: 1 bit": [
        {
            "problem": "5 + 3",
            "answer": "8"
        },
        {
            "problem": "5 - 3",
            "answer": "2"
        },
        {
            "problem": "9 + 6",
            "answer": "15"
        },
        {
            "problem": "9 - 6",
            "answer": "3"
        },
        {
            "problem": "7 + 4",
            "answer": "11"
        },
        {
            "problem": "7 - 4",
            "answer": "3"
        },
        {
            "problem": "12 + 8",
            "answer": "20"
        },
        {
            "problem": "12 - 8",
            "answer": "4"
        },
        {
            "problem": "15 + 5",
            "answer": "20"
        },
        {
            "problem": "15 - 5",
            "answer": "10"
        },
        {
            "problem": "3 + 1",
            "answer": "4"
        },
        {
            "problem": "3 - 1",
            "answer": "2"
        },
        {
            "problem": "6 + 2",
            "answer": "8"
        },
        {
            "problem": "6 - 2",
            "answer": "4"
        },
        {
            "problem": "10 + 7",
            "answer": "17"
        },
        {
            "problem": "10 - 7",
            "answer": "3"
        },
        {
            "problem": "8 + 3",
            "answer": "11"
        },
        {
            "problem": "8 - 3",
            "answer": "5"
        },
        {
            "problem": "14 + 9",
            "answer": "23"
        },
        {
            "problem": "14 - 9",
            "answer": "5"
        }
    ],
    "Medium: 10 bits": [
        {
            "problem": "12 x 3",
            "answer": "36"
        },
        {
            "problem": "12 / 3",
            "answer": "4"
        },
        {
            "problem": "8 x 4",
            "answer": "32"
        },
        {
            "problem": "8 / 4",
            "answer": "2"
        },
        {
            "problem": "9 x 3",
            "answer": "27"
        },
        {
            "problem": "9 / 3",
            "answer": "3"
        },
        {
            "problem": "10 x 2",
            "answer": "20"
        },
        {
            "problem": "10 / 2",
            "answer": "5"
        },
        {
            "problem": "7 x 1",
            "answer": "7"
        },
        {
            "problem": "7 / 1",
            "answer": "7"
        },
        {
            "problem": "6 x 6",
            "answer": "36"
        },
        {
            "problem": "6 / 6",
            "answer": "1"
        }
    ],
    "Hard: 30 bits": [
        {
            "problem": "(8 + 2) * 5",
            "answer": "50"
        },
        {
            "problem": "16 / (2 - 1) + 4",
            "answer": "20"
        },
        {
            "problem": "(5 + 3) * (2 + 1)",
            "answer": "24"
        },
        {
            "problem": "12 - (6 * 2)",
            "answer": "0"
        },
        {
            "problem": "10 + (20 / 5)",
            "answer": "14"
        },
        {
            "problem": "(15 - 5) * 3",
            "answer": "30"
        },
        {
            "problem": "40 / (8 + 2)",
            "answer": "4"
        },
        {
            "problem": "18 + (6 * 3)",
            "answer": "36"
        },
        {
            "problem": "(10 * 2) - 15",
            "answer": "5"
        },
        {
            "problem": "(30 / 3) + 7",
            "answer": "17"
        }
    ]
}